This matter
Это дело
Shall be handled as Minister Xie suggests
Сделаем как сказал министр Се
Since Your Highness has decided
Раз Ваше Высочество принял решение
This matter
Это дело
Leave it to me
позвольте мне заняться этим
I'll select a few trusted men
Я выберу несколько надёжных людей из своих
And handle it right away
Сейчас же займусь
Your Highness must stay calm
Ваше Высочество главное  сохраняйте хладнокровие
As for other matters
Остальное
This old minister
Старый слуга
Will arrange everything properly
я устрою
Make it clean
Сделай всё чисто
Yes
Да
Have you heard?
Слышали
That Chancellor Yu Gong of the Imperial Academy
Глава Академии Гоцзицзянь Юй Гун
Has been convicted of treason by the Imperial City Guard
обвинен Императорской стражей в измене
I heard they had accomplices
Говорят у него были сообщники
But overnight yesterday
но вчера за одну ночь
They all suddenly vanished
все внезапно исчезли
Yes
Да
No one knows where they went
неизвестно куда
His Majesty is unwell today
Сегодня Его Величество нездоров
No morning court
не проводить утреннюю аудиенцию
Gentlemen
Господа сановники
You may disperse
можете расходиться
Yes, understood
Хорошо да
Yes
Да
Your Highness, Prince of Jin
Принц Цзинь
Eunuch Wen
Вэньгунгун
His Majesty has an edict
Его Величество велел передать
Summoning you for a private audience
просит Вас на личную аудиенцию
Then
В таком случае
I trouble you, Eunuch
Побеспокою вас
Eunuch Wen
Евнух Вэнь
Father is not resting in his chambers
разве отец не отдыхает в покоях
His Majesty
Ваше Величество
Is in the Elixir Chamber, working on new pills
в алхимической лаборатории разрабатывает новый эликсир
Does the Eunuch know
А вы не знаете
Why Father wishes to see me alone?
Почему отец вызвал меня наедине
This old servant does not know
Старый слуга не в курсе